Phoebe.
Yeah?
Look at that guy
by the window.
Wow.
He's awfully short.
And I think
he's talking to himself.
And to be completely honest,
he's not that good in bed.
Oh, what is wrong
with me lately?
I mean, it's like
every guy I see...
I mean, okay, look at
that guy for example.
I mean, normally that's not
someone I would be attracted to
but right now,
with the way I'm feeling
all I want to do is rip off
his sweatpants and fanny pack.
Wait a second.
This is about the fourth month
of your pregnancy, right?
Yeah.
This is
completely normal.
Around the fourth month,
your hormones start going crazy.
Really? So this
has happened to you?
Oh, absolutely, yeah.
Oh, and keep in mind now,
I was carrying triplets.
So, you know,
in medical terms
I was thrice as randy.
Wow, this explains so much.
Last weekend,
I went from store to store
sitting on Santa's laps.
Yeah, yeah, I remember trying
to steal a cardboard cutout
of Evander Holyfield
from a Foot Locker.
Uh.
Yeah, oh.
Well, you know what, I go
see my doctor tomorrow.
I'll ask her about this.
Maybe she can give me
a pill or something.
Yeah, yeah, that's what
you need, a good pill.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey. Hi.
Hey.
Hi.
I got our pictures
developed from
Rockefeller Center.
Oh, great.
Hey, Joey
want to check out
pictures of me and
Mona ice skating?
Oh, uh... ordinarily
I would love to
but I am just swamped right now.
Where are the pictures that
that creepy pretzel vendor
took of us together?
Oh, yeah, probably
at the end.
Oh, my god.
All he took were
pictures of my breasts.
I'm missing picture time?
You know
she has a face, Ross.
Okay, okay, here's
a good one of us.
Wow, that is a good one.
Wow, looks like
a holiday card.
You know, with
the tree in the middle
and the skaters
and the snow.
You know, every year I say
I'm going to send
out holiday cards
and I never do it.
Do you want to send
this one out together?
Together?
L-Like to people?
Yeah, you know,
"Happy Holidays
from Mona and Ross."
It'll be cute, okay?
Okay.
Oh, I got to
get to work.
So call me later?
Oh, sure.
Bye, guys.
Bye.
Congratulations,
you just got married.
I know, can you
believe that?
Wait, I'm sorry
what's the big deal
about a holiday card?
Married couples
send out cards.
Families send out cards.
People who've been dating
for a couple of months
do not send out cards.
What, is she crazy?
Hey, hey, that's
your wife you're
talking about.
Bing!
Oh, and the Bingette.
Oh, honey, you remember
my boss Doug, right?
Yes, hi.
Hi. So, good news--
the divorce is final.
I sign the papers this a.m.
Oh, I didn't know
you and Carol
were getting a divorce.
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
Finally chewed my leg
out of that bear trap.
Hey
congratulations
to you guys, though.
Well, no leg chewing
for us, sir.
Well, give it time.
So, the divorce,
the marriage
we got a lot to celebrate.
How about we all go out
to dinner tomorrow night?
I can't think of
anything we're doing.
Why can't I think of
anything we're doing?
Tomorrow night it is then.
I should be out of court
by 6:00.
They keep throwing these
sexual harassment cases at me
and I keep knocking
them out of the park.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Just so you know,
we're not seeing him tomorrow.
I cannot spend another evening
with that man.
Do you remember
how he behaved at our wedding?
No.
That's because
he wasn't invited.
Because of the way he behaved
at our engagement party.
Oh, yeah.
Boy, urine
cuts right through
an ice sculpture,
doesn't it?
( knocking on door )
Hi.
Hey.
Hey, I went by the photo shop.
Take a look.
Here is a mock-up
of our card.
What do you think?
Huh. Wow, that's great.
Now do you think it should
say, "Love, Ross and Mona"?
Well, we haven't said
that to each other yet
but... I guess it's okay
to say it to other people.
How many did you want?
I'm getting 100.
A hundred?
Well, I, uh, I guess
I'll take, uh...
Mona...
I-I don't... I'm not sure
about the whole, uh...
the card thing.
Really, why not?
Sending out
a holiday card together...
I just don't know
if we're really quite there yet.
You know, I didn't
think of it that way.
You're right... you're right.
So can I ask you
a question?
Yeah.
Where are we?
Huh?
You know...
like where are we?
Where is this
relationship going?
Hmm.
I mean, I love spending
time with you, you know?
I just hope we're
moving forward.
We should probably
talk about that,
don't you think?
Let's do the card.
What?
The card.
I think we're there.
Okay.
But I still think we should
have this conversation.
( squeaks ):
Really?
I mean...
even with the card?
( knocking on door )
Hi.
Just so you know
Dr. Long can't
be here today
she was called
to the hospital.
So Dr. Schiff
will be seeing you.
Oh, okay.
Hey, can I ask you a question?
Was it me or was the guy
who took my blood sample
really cute?
You know who I'm talking about,
bowl haircut, hairy fingers.
( knocking )
Hi, Rachel?
I'm Dr. Schiff.
Yes, you are.
So how's it going?
Oh, it's really,
really good.
But enough about me, come on.
Where are you from?
What do you do?
I'm a doctor.
Right... right.
Actually, I meant
you know, in your spare time.
Do you cook? Do you ski?
Or just hang out
with your wife or girlfriend?
Uh, I don't have
a wife or a girlfriend
but I do like to ski.
Oh, I love to ski.
How amazing is this?
So, are you experiencing
any discomfort?
No, I'm very comfortable.
Any painful gas?
No.
Ooh, Dr. Schiff,
what kind of question is that?
Okay then.
Would you like to lie
down on the table?
Well, would you like me
to lie down on the table?
I'm sorry, is there
something going on here?
Do you feel it, too?
Hi.
Oh, hey, so?
How did your doctor's
appointment go?
Well, let's see
uh, they gave me
cute boy doctor today.
And in the middle of the exam
I put my pinkie
in his chin dimple.
Oh, my god.
Why did you do that?
Okay, remember that little
problem I was having
during my fourth month
of pregnancy?
Oh, yeah, the Evander
Holyfield phase.
Oh, man,
you were so hard up
you practically
came on to me.
You wish.
Hey, I could've had you
if I wanted you.
Oh, yeah?
Come and get it.
Okay, even this
is turning me on.
Hey.
Oh, hey.
Hey, Ross.
Hey, how's it going
with you and Mona?
Are you guys still together?
Oh, yeah, yeah,
we're moving forward.
You'll be getting our card.
You and Mona are doing
a holiday card together?
Yeah, we're not just
doing a card.
She also wants to have
the conversation
about where
the relationship is going.
Ugh, women.
I know, I know.
Why do you guys need to
have this conversation, huh?
I mean, no self-respecting man
would ask a woman
"So where's this going?"
Uh, Ross, you asked me that.
Hey, you were
a closed book, okay?
I'm not a mind reader.
Besides, I hate
those conversations.
I'm horrible at them, really.
Maybe I need some kind
of a gesture.
You know, something that says
we're moving forward
without having to talk about it.
Like asking her
to move in with you?
Wh-ha...
Smaller than that.
Making her a mix tape?
Uh, bigger than that.
Give her a key
to your apartment.
Whoa, hello?
We were closer
with the mix tape.
Have you said "I love you"?
You could say
"I love you."
Yeah, I don't... I don't think
I'm quite there yet.
But, oh! I could say "I love
spending time with you."
No, we hate that.
That is a slap
in the face.
Oh, forget it.
You know what, I'll just...
I'll have the conversation.
I'll just say "I like things
the way they are"
and hope for the best.
What do you think, Rach?
I think if it was
a little colder in here
I could see your nipples
through that sweater.
Bing. We're all set
for tonight. 8:00.
Oh, uh, as it turns out,
we can't do it.
Monica has to work.
Oh. My ex-wife didn't work.
Unless you call turning
into her mother work.
Yeah. Fine.
Tomorrow night, then.
Oh, uh, well, tomorrow's
no good for her, either.
Oh? Why not?
It's the semifinals...
of her...
bocci ball tournament.
What's going on, Bing?
Does, uh, your wife
have a... problem
with me or something?
Well, now you're... you're
just talking crazy.
Then why can't the three
of us go out together?
Because we-we-we split up.
Monica and I split up.
Hold me.
Good... good God, Bing, I...
Well, I can't say
I'm altogether surprised.
I saw the way she looked
at you, and...
there was no love there.
And the way she looked
at me. Pure lust.
You know what would
really help me
through this tough time
is choking someone.
Can I choke ya?
Mmm. Bing, my boy
we're going to get
you over this.
Now, here's the plan.
Grab your coat.
We're going to a strip club.
Oh, no, no, no.
Monica would freak.
But to hell with that bitch.
Here we go.
Mona, um
I think it's time
we had a conversation
about where things are
with us.
Yeah, I think
I suggested that.
Oh, we-we are so...
So, um...
Well, I-I really like you
and I love, um, you know,
hanging out with you
and, I mean, I'm having
a lot of fun.
Okay...
I mean, there's no point
in spending time with someone
if it's just fun.
I mean, it's got to be...
it's got to be going
somewhere, right?
( nervous chuckle )
So, where is it going?
Ah!
That's... that's
the real question.
And the answer is...
it's going somewhere... fun.
Now, I, I know
what you're thinking.
Fun was fine for you,
like, ten years ago
you know, but you're not
getting any younger.
No-- I mean
you know, not you,
you are getting younger.
I mean, you, you look like
you're getting younger
by the... by the second.
What's your secret?
I'm sorry. So, uh...
So where are we?
Well, well, to sum up...
We're having fun.
You look young.
Okay...
But that's not enough.
So... so...
Here's a key
to my apartment.
Really?
Really.
You don't think
this is too fast?
( tortured, falsetto grunt):
Mm-mm!
Not just a key.
I gave her the only key.
I am now a homeless person
in a very serious relationship.
Hey... oh, Ross. How'd
the conversation go?
Oh, great. I live
on the street.
Where?
Hey.
RACHEL:
Hi.
Okay, Monica, Rachel.
This is my friend, Roger.
Hi, Roger.
So, um, I'm going to get
us some drinks.
Could you help me out?
Yeah. Okay.
Um... he's here to have
sex with you.
What? What?
You're welcome.
Phoebe, no!
It's okay.
He's a virgin.
Rachel, um, I was
just talking to this guy
and I think he'll
have sex with you.
Okay, um...
Yeah, okay, let's leave
these two alone.
( spluttering )
No! You guys, I don't care
what my hormones are doing.
I am not going to just do it
with some random guy.
Fine. Then you tell Roger
because he was really
looking forward to this.
Excuse me.
Oh, baby.
Look at those twin
sisters dancing together.
Let me buy you
a lap dance
with those girls, huh?
Oh, that's all right, sir.
And that's just one girl.
Bing... what's this?
It's a hand.
It's a thing you use
as a Jack-and-coke holder.
No. It's a wedding ring.
You gotta get rid of it.
We're going to go to
the East River right
now and throw it in there!
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
I did and then I felt
a hell of a lot better
and if you whip it
just right
you might hit a seagull
in the head.
Okay. Oh, and I'm going
to need a bunch of extra keys.
Uh, apparently, I give them
away for no reason at all.
Hey, Ross.
What's going on?
You changing the lock?
No. That guy is.
I don't understand.
Y-you give me a key
to your apartment
and then you change
the lock.
Um...
Good luck, buddy.
Um, I... I thought we
were moving forward
and now you're, you're sending
me all these mixed signals.
What are you trying to tell me?
I'm trying to tell you
I made you a mix tape.
What?
I love you.
Oh... Oh!
And I love spending time
with you.
( door opens )
Hi, honey, I'm home.
From the tequila factory?
It was awful.
To get out of going
to dinner with Doug
I told him that you and I
split up
so then he took me
to all these strip clubs
and sleazy bars.
And then, when I wouldn't
give him my wedding ring
he threw a soda can
at a bird.
Come here.
I can breathe
through my mouth.
Oh, sweetie.
You know what the worst
part was?
I got to see what my life
would be like without you.
You know, it was like
It's a Wonderful Life
with lap dances.
Please promise me
that you will never leave me
that we will
grow old together
and be with each other
for the rest of our lives.
I promise.
Hey, speaking of together
how about we send out
a holiday card this year.
Ooh. I don't know
if we're there yet.
Yes, hi.
I'd like to order a pizza.
Oh, hey,
can I ask you a question?
Is the cute blond guy
delivering tonight?
Very Abercrombie & Fitch?
I'll call you back.
Who was that?
It's just the pizza place.
Y-you hung up
on the pizza place?
I don't hang up
on your friends.
Sorry, honey,
I'm just having a...
having a rough day.
Oh. What's wrong?
Oh, you really...
you really just don't
want to hear about it.
Then why did I ask?
Okay, it's just... and this
is really embarrassing
but lately, with this
whole pregnancy thing
I'm just finding myself...
how do I put this?
Um...
Erotically charged.
Is that college talk
for "horny?"
Yeah.
So, you know, I have all
of these feelings
and I don't know what to do
about them
because I can't date
like a normal person
which is fine, because I don't
need a relationship.
I mean, all I really want
is one great night.
Just sex, you know?
No strings attached,
no relationship
just... with someone
that I feel comfortable with
and who knows
what he's doing.
For just one great night.
I mean, is that really so...
hard... to find?
Well, so how was your day?
G-Good. I, uh, saw
a pretty big pigeon.
Well, I got to get up early
and it's almost 7:00, so...
Yeah, I got to go
to my room, too.
Okay, good night.
Good night.
I can't do it!
I didn't ask you
to do it!
You're Rachel!
You're Joey!
You're my friend!
Right back at ya!
Yeah... plus, it would be wrong
and weird and bad.
And so bad. But I don't even
know what you're talking about
because I didn't ask you
to do anything!
I know!
You want to do it?
No!
Me, neither!
I'm just testing you!
Hey, well, that's the end
of this conversation.
This conversation
never happened.
Never happened.
Good night.
Get back in there!
Hi.
Listen, I'm sorry about
that whole thing with Roger.
It really wasn't right
and I want to make it
up to you
so, um, I brought you
something that I think
you'll really enjoy. Okay.
Now, this is just
a loan, okay?
I'm going to want
him back, so.
I'm going to go now.
I'm sorry. I thought
I could do it, and I can't.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org